export const openTriviaApiUrl = 'https://opentdb.com'

export const mockQuestions = [
  {
    type: 'multiple',
    difficulty: 'medium',
    category: 'mock category',
    question: 'mock question',
    correct_answer: 'mock correct answer',
    incorrect_answers: [
      'mock incorrect answer 1',
      'mock incorrect answer 2',
      'mock incorrect answer 3'
    ]
  },
  {
    type: 'boolean',
    difficulty: 'medium',
    category: 'mock category',
    question: 'mock question 2',
    correct_answer: 'False',
    incorrect_answers: ['True']
  },
  {
    type: 'multiple',
    difficulty: 'medium',
    category: 'mock category',
    question: 'mock question 3',
    correct_answer: 'mock correct answer',
    incorrect_answers: [
      'mock incorrect answer 1',
      'mock incorrect answer 2',
      'mock incorrect answer 3'
    ]
  },
  {
    type: 'boolean',
    difficulty: 'medium',
    category: 'mock category',
    question: 'mock question 4',
    correct_answer: 'True',
    incorrect_answers: ['False']
  },
  {
    type: 'multiple',
    difficulty: 'medium',
    category: 'mock category',
    question: 'mock question 5',
    correct_answer: 'mock correct answer',
    incorrect_answers: [
      'mock incorrect answer 1',
      'mock incorrect answer 2',
      'mock incorrect answer 3'
    ]
  },
  {
    type: 'boolean',
    difficulty: 'medium',
    category: 'mock category',
    question: 'mock question 6',
    correct_answer: 'False',
    incorrect_answers: ['True']
  },
  {
    type: 'multiple',
    difficulty: 'medium',
    category: 'mock category',
    question: 'mock question 7',
    correct_answer: 'mock correct answer',
    incorrect_answers: [
      'mock incorrect answer 1',
      'mock incorrect answer 2',
      'mock incorrect answer 3'
    ]
  },
  {
    type: 'boolean',
    difficulty: 'medium',
    category: 'mock category',
    question: 'mock question 8',
    correct_answer: 'True',
    incorrect_answers: ['False']
  },
  {
    type: 'multiple',
    difficulty: 'medium',
    category: 'mock category',
    question: 'mock question 9',
    correct_answer: 'mock correct answer',
    incorrect_answers: [
      'mock incorrect answer 1',
      'mock incorrect answer 2',
      'mock incorrect answer 3'
    ]
  },
  {
    type: 'boolean',
    difficulty: 'medium',
    category: 'mock category',
    question: 'mock question 10',
    correct_answer: 'False',
    incorrect_answers: ['True']
  }
]
